[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wally the Green Monster is the mascot for which sports team?", "correct_answer": "Boston Red Sox", "incorrect_answers": ["Cincinnati Reds", "Baltimore Orioles", "Chicago White Sox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred in the 1982 science fiction movie Blade Runner as Rick Deckard?", "correct_answer": "Harrison Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["Bruce Willis", "John Travolta", "Sean Connery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The two terms nephro and ren both refer to the kidneys.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The self-governed region of the Holy Mountain is considered part of the Greek state according to a decree\npassed in what year?", "correct_answer": "1913", "incorrect_answers": ["1910", "1925", "1999"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much blood does the average adult human have?", "correct_answer": "10-12 pints (5-6 liters)", "incorrect_answers": ["10-12 gallons (38-45 liters)", "10-12 quarts (10-11 liters)", "4-8 pounds (2-4 kg)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is the capital and largest city of Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Antananarivo", "incorrect_answers": ["Fianarantsoa", "Mahajanga", "Toliara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wilhelm Kolff invented what device?", "correct_answer": "Dialysis machine", "incorrect_answers": ["Football helmet", "Linotype machine", "PET scan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a patient presents with a sore throat, which of the following diagnoses may indicate immediate intubation?", "correct_answer": "Epiglottitis", "incorrect_answers": ["Mononucleosis", "Quinsy", "Peri-tonsillar Abscess"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This place, popular as the center of the Whiskey rebellion, is the worlds first nuclear powered city.", "correct_answer": "Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania", "incorrect_answers": ["San Diego, CA", "Baltimore", "Washington, D.C."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2001 Freddy Got Fingered won all five major Razzies (Worst Film, Worst Actor, Worst Actress, Worst Director, Worst Screenplay). Who was the star of this film?", "correct_answer": "Tom Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Dice Clay", "Timothy Patrick", "Seth Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "if the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be age 65 or older?", "correct_answer": "74", "incorrect_answers": ["223", "195", "364"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diet of the koala consists mainly of what plant species?", "correct_answer": "Eucalyptus", "incorrect_answers": ["Bamboo", "Willow", "Cork Oak"]}]